[{"answer": "What do you think", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yeah, yeah like him, definitely like him. I like him a lot", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Ask your mother, you live with her now, don't you? Anyway, so then this guy comes up to me and starts feeling my jacket through his thumb and his forefinger like this", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I sai", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "my friend, where did you get that sweater", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I think that's what the back of closets are for. my friend looks out the windo", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What was all that sniffing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You don't think...", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Then, what was all that sniffing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Today is not cold", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Do we have to...", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "They are made from lycr", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Take a look", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I don't know what the big problem is getting a bra?", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Look, it doesn't necessarily mean anything yet, it just means he was sniffing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No, he didn't use 'man'", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I got a few messages, I wrote them down", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Lets see, they are...here they are", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Thank you. Heh, I'll call you back.Ooh, my friend had the baby! Oh, my God that's wonderful! Who called", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "She did? Oh, that's so great", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "So", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What's so curious about it", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What's so curious about it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Well, maybe I don't use my exclamation points as haphazardly as you do", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, I mean if one of your close friends had a baby and I left you a message about it, I would use an exclamation point", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You don't think that someone having a baby warrants an exclamation point", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "It's an exclamation point! It's a line with a dot under it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "A call for one, you know I thought I've heard everything. I've never heard a relationship being affected by a punctuation", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Yes, I'd like to speak to my friend, please", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Out of town", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Out of town", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "So what", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "People go to that place", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "It's Thursday", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Tuesday has no feel. Monday has a feel, Friday has a feel, Sunday has a feel...", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Really? Feels like Tuesday", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I feel Tuesday and Wednesday..", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I've should've gone in with him", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "What you need me in the car for", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Excuse me, I have to go to the bathroom", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Hip to the what", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "You know this... Knock on the door. It's pizzagu", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Sniffing-Accountant.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Hi my friend", "qsentId": 44}]